Guide to the Noël Riley Fitch Julia Child Papers MSS.323
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Appetite for Life: The Biography of Julia Child, 219572
  - Subseries A: Research Files, 219573
    - Southern California Culinary Guild Honors Paul Child, 1987, 1989; 227272 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Fat - 1988 [Photocopies of Letters], 1988, 1990s; 227275 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Clippings - 1989, 1989, 1994 - 1996; 227276 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - The Way to Cook: Promo 1989, 1989, 1994 - 1996; 227279 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - 1990s, undated, 1994; 227284 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - 1990 Articles, 1990s; 227286 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - A.I.W.F. Tour - Rebuilding, 1990 - 1991; 227289 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Clippings - 1991, 227292 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Clippings - 1992, 1992, 1994; 227293 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Julia Child Contributions to The Horn of Plenty and "Resetting the American Table": 1964 - 1965, 1992, undated, 1965; 227296 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Merci, Julia [Programs, Articles], 1990s; 227299 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Clippings - 1993, 1993, 1994; 227301 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Animal Rights Food Fears [See also Fat Folder, Original Letter], various; 227303 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Feuds / Scandals Plagiarism [Ch. 25 1983/4], 1990s; 227304 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Homosexuals - Gay, 1982, 1992; 227306 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Cooking With the Master Chefs, 1993, 1996; 227308 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - A.I.W.F. 1991+, 1990s; 227311 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Restaurant / Food News - 1994, 227312 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Clippings - 1994, 227314 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Paul's Death (Religious), 1994; 227316 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - TVFN - Premiere November 23, 1993, Taping April 1994, 1993 - 1995; 227319 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - 1995 January - June, 1994, 1995; 227320 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - 1995 July - December, 227321 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Internet - Julia Child, 1995 - 1997; 227324 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - 1995 Food World, 227326 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Baking at Julia's, 1995 - 1996; 227327 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Morrow - '96, 227328 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Cooking in Concert / Pepin & Kerr, 1995 - 1996; 227329 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - 1996 Food World, 227330 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - 1996 January - July, 227331 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - 1996 August - December, 227332 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - A.I.W.F. 1996 - 1997, 227333 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - 1997 January - May, 227334 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - 1997 June - December, 227336 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - 1997 Food World, 227338 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - 1998 Food World, 227339 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - 1998 Julia Child, 227340 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Fame - Celebrity, 1993 - 1994; 227341 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Doctoral Degrees, 1996 - 1997; 227343 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Last Meal (& Claiborner More) - '75, 1975, 1996; 227345 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Questions for Julia, 1996; 227403 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 1999 Julia Child, 1998 - 1999; 227404 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - 1999 Food World, 1990s; 227405 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Estate, 1984, 1994; 227406 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Julia's Fame (Porn), undated; 227407 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Copia - 90th Birthday, 2002; 227408 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Copia, 2001 - 2002; 227409 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - 2000, 227410 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - 2001, 2001 - 2002; 227411 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Smithsonian, 2002 - 2003; 227412 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Quotes and Subtitles, 1993, undated; 227413 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Julia's Death - August 2004, 227414 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Julia - The Net, 1996 - 1997; 227419 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Acknowledgements, 1994, 1996, undated; 227420 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - End of Book (Partially Corrected), undated; 227421 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Appendix: Anti - McCarthy Letter, Harvard [Photocopies], 1954, 1997; 227422 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Bibliography, 1997, undated; 227423 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Genealogy Section, 1997; 227424 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - McWilliams Family Tree, 1995, 1997; 227425 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Family Trees, 1997; 227426 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Child Family Tree, 1997; 227427 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Weston Family Tree, undated; 227428 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - McWilliams Family [Original Letters], 1967 - 1968, undated; 227429 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Father - John McWilliams [Original Documentation], various; 227430 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Recollections of John McWilliams [Book with Notation], 1919, undated; 227431 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Mother - Carolyn (Caro) Weston, 1994; 227432 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Weston Family [Original Documentation], 1971, 1994, 1996; 227481 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Weston 1065 - 1951 [Family Record Book], 227482 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - "Excerpts from the 1865 - 1897 Diaries of My Grandmother Julia Mitchell Weston" by Katharine Weston Crane [Photocopy], undated; 227483 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Pittsfield, MA - Weston, 1993 - 1994; 227484 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Child Family, 1988, 1993 - 1994; 227485 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Timeline [20 of 111 People], November 1996; 227486 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Child Addresses for Appetite, 1996; 227487 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Certificates / Passports, 1993; 227488 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - State Department, 1993 - 1997; 227489 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - OSS - CIA, 1993 - 1995; 227492 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - FBI - Justice Department, 1993, 1998; 227493 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - U.S. Information Agency, 1993, 1998; 227494 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Finding Aid: Simone "Simca" Beck Papers, September 1995; 227495 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Finding Aid: Julia Child Papers, Schlesinger Library, November 1993; 227496 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Schlesinger - Radcliffe [Notes, Correspondence], 1995, 1997; 227497 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Bouillabaisse Gail [Original Documentation], 1967, 1994; 227498 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Coq au Vin, 1957 - 1958, undated; 227499 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Quiche - Barbara Hall, 1995, 1997; 227500 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Pot au Feu, 1990; 227501 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Reine de Saba, 1997; 227529 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Julia Child 2003, 2003 - 2004; 227553 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Julia Child 2004, 2004, 2006; 227554 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Julia Child 2005 - 2006, 227555 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Food Articles, 1982, 2000; 227556 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Julia Child: Bios, Resumes, various; 227557 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Julia Child Timeline, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - University Collections -- Child, 1977-2004 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Julia C. Diaries (1960 is Original, the Rest Copies), Related, 1960, 2009-2011, undated (Box 27, Folder 3-4)
  - Subseries B: Research Correspondence, 219581
    Subseries B: Research Correspondence consists of correspondence between Noël Riley Fitch and Julia Child's family, friends, colleagues, acquaintances, as well as Child herself and those influenced by her. It is arranged alphabetically according to the name of the correspondent or institution, except for correspondence between Julia Child and Noël Riley Fitch which has been retained together at the end of the subseries.
    - Potential Source Names, 1992, 1994; 227558 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Names + Addresses, 1993, 1996; 227559 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Ackerman, Marshall, 1997; 227561 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Alex, Kathie, 1993 - 1994, 1997; 227562 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Allegro, Antonia, 1996 - 1997; 227560 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Alssid, Rebecca: Boston University, 1997 - 1999; 227563 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Apple, R.W. [John], 2001 - 2002; 227564 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Bain, David [Breadloaf], 1993; 227565 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Baltrusaitis, Hélène, 1978, 1993 - 1994, 2009; 227566 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Barassart, Elisabeth - Cordon Bleu, 1992 - 1993; 227567 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Barr, Nancy Verde, 1982, 1985, 1993, 1995; 227568 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Beales, Mary Zook - Katharine Branson School, 1994; 227569 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Beard House [James Beard Foundation], 1996; 227570 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Bear Dallis, Martha, 2001; 227571 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Beck, Emily Brooks (Wendy) - Lawyer, 1996; 227572 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Becton, Henry - WGBH President, 1996 - 1997; 227573 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Bedford, Sybille, 1978, 1998; 227574 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Belin, Mary Cootes, 1993, 2002; 227575 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Berman, Fran - PR NYC, 1998; 227576 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Berrard, Ailene Martin, 1994; 227577 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Berk, Karen, 1997, 2000; 227578 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Bertholle, Louisette (Madame La Contesse D'Naleche), 1967, 1976, 1983, 1992; 227604 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Bicknell, [Peter and Mari], 1993 - 1994; 227605 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Bissell, Frances and Tom, 1994 - 2001; 227606 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Black, Corinne, 1993 - 1994, 1996; 227607 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Bollinger, Jane, 1996; 227608 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Brochas, Beverly DC, 1998; 227609 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Boston University, 1996, 1998; 227610 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Boteler, Alison, 1980s, 1990s; 227611 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Brennan, Fanny, 1983, 1993 - 2001; 227612 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Breuster, Joan (Edith Kennedy, Paul - Poet), 1995; 227613 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Brown, Benjamin, 1996; 227614 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Brown, Diane Harris - Beard House, 1994, 1997; 227615 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Brown, Philip S., 1994; 227616 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Bryant, Barbara Ord, 1994; 227617 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Burde, Constance Hamilton, 1995, 1997 - 1998; 227618 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Burros, Marian, 1995 - 1996; 227619 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Cairns, Mary Ford, 1994; 227620 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Cannon, Lou and Mary, undated; 227621 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Carhartt, Thomas, 1993; 227622 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Carter, Page, 1993; 227623 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Casella, Cesare, 2002; 227624 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Chamberlain, Narcisse, 1982, 1994; 227626 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Child, Jonathan, 1993, 1994; 227627 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - From Julia's File, 1994 - 1996; 227638 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - [Child], Julia - Noel Riley Fitch and Bert Sonnnenfield, 1992 - 2004; 227639 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Child, Rachel, 1993 - 1997; 227640 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Claasen, Lynda - UCSD, 1994 - 1999; 227641 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Clark, Robert, 1993 - 1994; 227642 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Claiborne, Craig, 1995; 227652 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Clopper, Pat Brown, 1996 - 1998; 227655 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Cobb, Nancy, 2007, 2010; 227658 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Cointreau, André - Cordon Bleu, 1993 - 1994, 1996; 227660 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Coolidge, J.R., 1994 - 1998; 227662 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Cory, Constance (Connie) Thayer, 1994; 227663 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Cousins, Dorothy, 1970, 1990s; 227664 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Cousins, Philadelphia, 1994 - 2011; 227669 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Cousins, Sam, 1993 - 1994; 227672 (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Crotinger, Howard - Marseille, 1994 - 1995; 227690 (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Culbertson, Martha, 1994 - 1995, 1997; 227691 (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Cunningham, Marian, 1996 - 1999; 227692 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Cutler, Carol, 1995 - 1998; 227723 (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Culinary HIstorians A. [Leaf] February 3rd, 1998, 2000; 227724 (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Culinary History FCI Launch, 1997; 227725 (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Davidson, Alan, 1999; 227726 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - Davidson, Susy, 1992, 1994, 1997; 227727 (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Davies, Elton, 1993; 227728 (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Davidson, Peter, 1994 - 1996; 227729 (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - Delf, Joy, 1996 - 1997; 227730 (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - Del Grande, Robert and Anni, 1997; 227731 (Box 9, Folder 72)
    - Delécluse, Sylvie, 1994 - 1995; 227732 (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - Derven, Daphne, 1997 - 2010; 227733 (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - De Santis, Carl, 1996; 227734 (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - De Voto, [Mark], 1994 - 1995; 227735 (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - Dietrickson, Jan / Frøydis - Oslo, 1994 - 1997; 227736 (Box 9, Folder 77)
    - Doerr, Harriet, 1996; 227737 (Box 9, Folder 78)
    - Dorra, Mary, 1994; 227738 (Box 9, Folder 79)
    - Downing, John P. - Avon, 1994; 227739 (Box 9, Folder 80)
    - Drummond, Geoffrey - A La Carte Prud., 1994 - 1996, 2010 - 2011; 227740 (Box 9, Folder 81)
    - du Couedic, Madame F., 1995; 227741 (Box 9, Folder 82)
    - Duemlinn, Robert, 1971, 1995; 227742 (Box 9, Folder 83)
    - Dunaway, Suzanne, 2000, 2008, 2011; 227743 (Box 9, Folder 84)
    - D ' Vari, Marisa, 1998 - 1999; 227744 (Box 9, Folder 85)
    - Echikson, William - Loiseaux, 1995; 227745 (Box 9, Folder 86)
    - Egge, Bjørn / Eline, 1995; 227746 (Box 9, Folder 87)
    - Estabrook, Reed F., 1994; 227747 (Box 9, Folder 88)
    - Fabricant, Florence, 1995, 1997; 227748 (Box 9, Folder 89)
    - Fairchild, Barbara, 2002, 2006; 227749 (Box 9, Folder 90)
    - Fairley, E. Lee and Gisela, 1995 - 1997; 227750 (Box 9, Folder 91)
    - Faison, George, 1996 - 1997; 227827 (Box 9, Folder 92)
    - Feniger, Susan and Milliken, Mary Sue, 1997; 227828 (Box 9, Folder 93)
    - Fenzl, Barbara Pool (Terry) Phoenix, 1993 - 1999; 227829 (Box 9, Folder 94)
    - Ferguson, Priscilla Parkhurst - Columbia, 1995 - 1997; 227830 (Box 9, Folder 95)
    - Ferrone, John, 1974, 1994, 1997; 227831 (Box 9, Folder 96)
    - Few, Lyne S. [Ellen], 1994 - 1995, 1997; 227832 (Box 9, Folder 97)
    - Field, Carol, 1994 - 2003; 227833 (Box 9, Folder 98)
    - Fisher, Lisbeth, 1995; 227834 (Box 9, Folder 99)
    - Fletcher, Janet, 1996; 227835 (Box 9, Folder 100)
    - Fletcher, Ron, 1993; 227836 (Box 9, Folder 101)
    - Fondulas, Ted / Lynn, 1994, 1998; 227837 (Box 9, Folder 102)
    - Ford, Terry, 1996; 227838 (Box 9, Folder 103)
    - Frank, Ken, 1996 - 1997; 227839 (Box 9, Folder 104)
    - Franey, Pierre, 1995 - 1996; 227840 (Box 9, Folder 105)
    - Friedman, Jane, 1982, 1995 - 1997; 227841 (Box 9, Folder 106)
    - Friendly, Jean - Marshall Plan, paris, 1996; 227842 (Box 9, Folder 107)
    - Fullerton, James, 1993; 227843 (Box 9, Folder 108)
    - Fussell, Betty, 1994-2015; 227844 (Box 9, Folder 109, Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Galbraith, JK and Kitty (and Catherine Atwater), 1993, 1997, 2006; 227845 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Gates, Mrs. Freeman / Katy, 1982, 1993, 1995; 227846 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Gewertz, Catherine, 1996; 227847 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Gibson, Charlie, 1996; 227848 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Gifford, Dun, 1994 - 1997; 227849 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Goldkang, Janice - Publicity Knopf, 1994 - 1995; 227850 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Graff, Richard, 1996; 227851 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Greenspan, Dorie, 1996, 1999; 227852 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Gruenwald, George, 1995 - 1997; 227853 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Haber, Barbara, 1993 - 2011; 227925 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Hall, Charles, 1994; 227926 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Hallor, Orian Hall (Babe), 1994 - 1997; 227927 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Hansen, Viola (Tuckerman) [Mrs. Siguard Hansen] - Kathatine Branson School, 1994; 227928 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Hamilton, Dorothy Cann, 1995 - 2012; 227929 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Hargraves, Michael, 1996 - 1997, 2001; 227930 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Harris, Nancy Kirby, 1996; 227933 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Hastings, Robert P., 1995 - 1996; 227934 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Hastings - Black, Julia - St. Ange, 1994, 2006; 227935 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Hatch, Nancy (Gregg), 1996; 227938 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Hazan, Marcella / Victor, 1996 - 1997; 227942 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Healy, Harriet, 1994 - 1996; 227943 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Hector, Louis, 1994 - 1997; 227945 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Hemingway, Jack, 1994 - 1997; 227963 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Henstell, Pamela, 1993 - 1996; 227947 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Hersh, Stephanie, 1994 - 2009; 227949 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Hess, Karin (John), 1994 - 1995; 227953 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Heyerdahl, Jens, 1995 - 1996; 227955 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Hier, Fritz, 1996; 227956 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Hiscock, Alice C. [Mrs. Earle], 1994 - 1995; 227958 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Hovey, Anita Hinckley, 1994, 1997; 227959 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Howe, Fisher / Debby, 1994 - 1997; 227960 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Huffman, Sue, 1995 - 1999; 227965 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - [Hull], Barbara, 2009; 227966 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Huttenback, Robert (Bob), 1994 - 1997; 227967 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Hyman, Phil and Mary, 1993 - 2000; 227968 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Jacobs, J. Roland, 1995; 227969 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Jacobson, Susan, 1996; 227970 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Jenkins, Nancy Harmon, 1994 - 1997; 227971 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Johnson, Anne Winston - Smith, 1995 - 1996; 227972 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Jones, Jeffrey - Veterans of OSS, 1994; 227973 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Jones, Judith, 1993 - 2000; 227975 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Joseph, Jennifer, 2009; 227978 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Letters from Journalists, 1994 - 2002; 227980 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Kafka, Barbara, 1993 - 1996; 227982 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Kamman, Madeleine, 1994 - 2009; 227984 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Kase, Betty Parker, 1993 - 1994; 227985 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Kasper, Lynne Rossetto, 1994 - 1995; 227986 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Kennedy, Edmund, 1994; 227987 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Kenward, Tor, 2001; 227988 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Kerr, Graham, 1996 - 2006; 227990 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Konkel, Susan Donnell, 1995; 227991 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Klausner, Willette and Manny, 2002 - 2006; 227992 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Klugman, Roberta, 1994 - 1996; 227993 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Koshland, William, 1993 - 1997; 227994 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Kostic, Harriet - KBS, 1993 - 1994; 227995 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Kubler, Betty and George, 1994 - 1995; 227996 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Kump, Peter and Christopher, 1990 - 1997; 227997 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Leaf, Alexandra - FCI Conference, 1996; 227998 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Levy, Paul - England, 1993 - 2009; 227999 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Lisle, (Bill), 1994; 228000 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Lobrano, Alec, 2002 - 2009; 228001 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Lockwood, Ruth, 1993 - 1994, 1997; 228002 (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Londe, James [Noah] - Homophobia St. Louis, 1996 - 1997; 228004 (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Longone, Jan, 1990 - 2000; 228006 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Mah, Maggie, 1996; 228007 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Manell, Rosemary, 1993 - 1995; 228008 (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Manghise, Joseph, 1996; 228009 (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Martin, Byron - OSS, 1994 - 1998; 228010 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Martin, Dudley - "Homosexual Letter", 1992 - 1997; 228012 (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - Martin, Edward (Sandy), 1993; 228016 (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - Martin, Guy (Edith), 1994; 228018 (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - Martin, Tom / Anne, 1999 - 2001; 228019 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Mc Carty, Michael, 1997 - 2006; 228020 (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Mc Donald, James - Bonn, 1996 - 1997; 228021 (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - Mc Intosh, Elizabeth (Betty), 1993 - 2003; 228022 (Box 10, Folder 75)
    - Mc Williams, Alex, 1995 - 1997; 228023 (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - Mc Williams, David, 1993 - 1997; 228025 (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - Mc Williams III., John, 1993 - 2002; 228028 (Box 10, Folder 78)
    - Mc Williams, Patty, 1993 - 1994; 228030 (Box 10, Folder 79)
    - Mc Williams, Saba, 1995 - 1997; 228033 (Box 10, Folder 80)
    - Miall, Sally (Bicknell), 1994; 228035 (Box 10, Folder 81)
    - Michlin - Le Barry, 1997; 228037 (Box 10, Folder 82)
    - Middleton, Juliana, 1996; 228038 (Box 10, Folder 83)
    - Milbank, Helen Kirpatrick, 1995; 228039 (Box 10, Folder 84)
    - Miller, Bess, 1994; 228040 (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - Miller, Victoria Thorpe (Eleanor Clark Biography), 1996 - 1997; 228041 (Box 10, Folder 86)
    - Molard, Jane Owen, 1996; 228045 (Box 10, Folder 87)
    - Mondaui, Robert / Margrit Bieuer, 1992 - 1998; 228048 (Box 10, Folder 88)
    - Moore, John and Heidi, 1994 - 1997; 228049 (Box 10, Folder 89)
    - Morash, Russ and Marian, 1993 - 2003; 228050 (Box 10, Folder 90)
    - Moulton, Sara, 1994 - 2012; 228051 (Box 10, Folder 91)
    - Mowrer, Richard S., 1994 - 1995; 228052 (Box 10, Folder 92)
    - Nelson, Caritta, 1996; 228053 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Nelson, Kyle, 1996; 228055 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Nicol, Lizabeth, 1993 - 2004; 228058 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Noall, Ollie (Mrs. Hugh Fraser Noall), 1993 - 1994; 228060 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Olson, Deborah, 1994 - 1997; 228061 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Olney, Richard, 1994 - 2000; 228062 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - O'Neill, Carolyn, 1995 - 1996; 228063 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - O'Neill, Molly, 1995 - 1996; 228064 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Parker, Dana Gans, 1995; 228065 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Parsons, Russ, 1998 - 2008; 228066 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Patterson, Susy, 1993; 228067 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Pepin, Jacques, 1995 - 2006; 228068 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Perry Kathleen, 1993 - 1996; 228069 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Pool, Jean, 1996 - 1997; 228070 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Poole, Corinne - BC Restaurant, 1994; 228072 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Pratt, Herbert and Pat, 1994 - 1998; 228073 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Prescott, Peter - Knopf History, 1993; 228074 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Prud' Homme, Erica Child (Hector), 1993 - 1997, 2011; 228075 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Puck, Wolfgang, 1999 - 2002; 228076 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Putzell, Edwin J. (Ned), 1994 - 1995; 228077 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Raichlen, Steven, 1995 - 1997; 228078 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Reardon, Joan, 1991 - 2004; 228079 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Rekhl, Ruth, 1999, 2001; 228080 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Riley, John E., 1992; 228081 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Ripley, Mary and Dillon, 1993 - 1994; 228082 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Risley, Mary - Director, Tante Marie's Cooking School, 1993 - 1997; 228084 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Rockwell, Stuart W., 1994; 228085 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Rosbottom, Betty, 1992 - 2011; 228087 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Rusconi, Natale, 1993, 1997; 228088 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Russell, Mary, 1993 - 1994; 228089 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - [de] Saint Phalle, Thibaut, 1994; 228096 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Savis, Shirley, 1977, 1996; 228094 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Sayet, Marsha - Norman's (Florida), 1997; 228097 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Scherer, Jim, 1994; 228098 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Schlesinger, Marian, 1997; 228099 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Schodt, Margie, 1994 - 1997; 228100 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Sharon - Emeril's Delmonico, 2002; 228101 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Sheeline, Paul, 1993 - 1994; 228102 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Sheldon, Virginia (Peachy), 1995; 228103 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Sheraton, Mimi, 1995 - 1997; 228104 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Simonds, Nina, 1997 - 1998; 228105 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Simmons, Roxane Ruhl - KBS, 1994 - 1997; 228106 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Sims - Bell, Barbara, 1994 - 1997; 228107 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Sloane, Joseph C., 1993 - 1997; 228108 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Smith, Catharine (Kitty Carton Swett Smith), 1995; 228111 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Solomon, Charmaine (Ceylon), 1993; 228112 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Sontheimer, Carl, 1995 - 1996; 228113 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Sparks, Katy, 2000 - 2006; 228114 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Speyer, Darthea, 1997; 228115 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Spitz, Bob, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Staglin, Shari and Garen, 2000 - 2002; 228116 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Stewart, Martha, 1994 - 2002; 228122 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Stewart, Zanne - Early Gourmet, 1995 - 2000; 228125 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Stieglitz, Perry (and Moune), 1994 - 1995; 228126 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Steingarten, Jeffrey, 1996 - 2002; 228128 (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Strada, David, 1997; 228129 (Box 11, Folder 55)